Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Research Department records, 1941-1983 IBT0010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- State Historical Society of Wisconsin Files, 1907-2003; Series 4; 1 Linear Feet
  - SHSW: American Federation of Labor Records Guide [1/2], undated; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - SHSW: American Federation of Labor Records Guide [2/2], 1981; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SHSW: International Brotherhood of Teamsters Records Guide [1/2], 1986-2002; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SHSW: International Brotherhood of Teamsters Records Guide [2/2], 1988-2003; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters/State Historical Society of Washington Correspondence, 1968-1996; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Reports, Series 5
  This series contains reports from the Research Department.
  - Michigan Conference of Teamsters Yearly Report Part 1, 1954; IBT0010 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Conference of Teamsters Yearly Report Part 2, 1954; IBT0010 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Pay Board News Releases, 1972; IBT0010 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Pay Board News Releases, 1972; IBT0010 (Box 20, Folder 4)